

0937-324-826 dumdumgenius@gmail.com Taiwan ,Taichung

Introduction

Hello, I'm Yi Chung Yang, I come from Taiwan and graduated from Chiao Tung
University. I have quick thinking and good knowledge of mathematics and
physics,. I got my bachelor degree of EE, but I chose to start my career as a developer with the simple
reason, I love programming. Also I spent lots of time studying some courses in Computer Science. Now
I'm a full-stack developer for about two years. I used Java, NodeJS to build up back-end (Most in JS), while
React.js in front-end. Also I know how to build up data-base, reverse proxy server and docker. I can speak
English, Japanese, Chinese, I've always been looking for a chance to work with people all over the world.

p.s: Must to see my website: http://serieshelper.dumdumgenius.com/

Techniques

- 1. Chinese, English, Japanese
- 2. 2 years Experience of Java, and JavaScript, especially in JavaScript.
- 3. ES6, ES7, and build up every kind of interface in CSS3 + HTML.
- 4. Familiar with front-end framework like Angular, React, and tools like webpack, gulp.
- 5. Basic knowledge on CS, like data structure, algorithm.
- 6. Know how to use **Docker** to quickly build up micro services.
- 7. Popular database like **Postgres**, MySQL and NoSQL database like **Mongo**.
- 8. Use git, and know the git flow.
- 9. Understanding **Linux** and some usual command.
- 10. Have experience on Amazone EC2, and know how to do gzip, cache, load balance by Nginx
- 11. Node.js and express and popular tool like JSLint, babel-node, nodemon.

Experience

NATURALTEL - 2015 - 05 ~ 2016 - 04 (JAVA ENGINNER)

Here're some important projects I was involved in.

IVR System:

It's a system which serves people when they call the number we provide. once the call connected, they will hear some voices that guide them to do some action like purchasing, querying account balance, change the default language and so on.

I finished this project with another partner, we use VXML language to deal with the action triggered by key input of phone, while using Java to build up our APIs.

Warning System:

In this project, we collect information of every user's phone call and store them in our database. And for about every hour, we will analyze those information and check if there's any problem with them, once we find the unusual case, we will send alert message to the person in charge of handling those errors.

I took charge in the most important part of this project, I write the data parser. In this parser I transfer the binary data to information and I do some magic that you can decide what kind of datas you want from those information and where to store them by not changing the code but just configure file. I use some concept of Data Structure, so even the data is big, we can still finish the job in short time.

SYNTRONTECH - 2016 - 04 - NOW (JAVASCRIPT ENGINEER)

In this company, I'm a full-stack engineer, and I built up a platform from zero with my partners.

Synhealth Platform:

It's a B2B platform, it is built for Direct Selling use. We have many roles like enterprise, agent, dealer, health carer and customer. You can use this platform to add some products or add new dealer or agent under a enterprise or you can make a deal with new health carer. What kind of jobs you can do in this platform are determined by which role you are, so it's a little complicated platform. Also we have an APP for customers, so we still need to build some API for APP to use.

I played the full stacker in here (actually we have four full stacker), so we arranged our jobs by features. As a new request came, we will tear it into parts and assess the time-cost of every part, finally send them to all members and start working.

Education

Chiao Tung University – Bachelor, 2009 - 09 ~ 2013 - 06

Studied at Electronic Engineering , but my best performance is in courses like Introduction to Computer Science and Object-Oriented and Java Programming, I also built up a game based on Java.

Youtube link: https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=dQCIN6kxwkE



Side Project

Series Helper:

It's composed of React + Redux + Server-side structure, ES6, Node + Express, MongoDB, also Docker, AWS EC2 and Nginx, I also used 3-rd party API of Facebook to help me authenticate the users. I used all new techniques I know to build it up.

Series Helper try to help anyone note down their progress of watching TV shows. With it, you can easily write down your progress in just some clicks, and all you need are browser and FB account.

Website: http://serieshelper.dumdumgenius.com/

React Redux Universal Starter Kit:

I built up this project to help me quickly start a React project based on Universal (Isomorphic) structure.

My purpose is providing someone who just want a simple structure rather than complicated one.

Project: https://github.com/DumDumGeniuss/react-universal-redux-starter-kit

Reference

Github: https://github.com/DumDumGeniuss

identity-name

Series Helper: http://serieshelper.dumdumgenius.com/

React Redux Universal Starter Kit: https://github.com/DumDumGeniuss/react-universal-redux-starter-kit